careersinmusic.com 2017-06-11

# CareersInMusic.com / Generation-Z | Privacy Policy

    _Last updated October 23, 2014_

This Privacy Policy outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected via this Website. Generation-Z provides this Privacy Policy to help users make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website. PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF ANY CHANGES. GENERATION-Z DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEBSITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO GENERATION-Z OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy applies to Generation-Z collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Generation-Z on its (a) websites, including all of its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the Website); (b) on various third party websites; and (c) to Generation-Z other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. Generation-Z is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications. By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Website Terms and Conditions. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official Generation-Z contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms and Conditions and/or other stated policies.

  1.  **Collection of Information.**

1.1 Survey Information. Generation-Z collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes a Generation-Z survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a Survey). (As used herein, online means using the Internet, including the Website, and related technologies, and offline means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, Generation-Z or a third party (a Third Party) may ask an individual to provide various information to Generation-Z, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, Survey Information). Generation-Z may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this Website. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Generation-Z or a Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from Generation-Z or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to Generation-Z.

1.2 Third Party List Information. Generation-Z collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and Generation-Z subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the Seller). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual’s name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, Third Party List Information). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Generation-Z seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Generation-Z and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller’s list.

1.3 Other Information. Other occasions when Generation-Z obtains information from individuals include: (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by Generation-Z or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through Generation-Z customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a Generation-Z service or newsletter (together, Other Information).

1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. Generation-Z currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, Generation-Z may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future.

 _(a)_ Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual’s computer that allows Generation-Z to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in the Generation-Z database. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website.  
 _(b)_ Web Beacons. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using a programming function but can also be used to transfer an individual’s unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Generation-Z to track certain websites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, Generation-Z might place, with the consent of a Third Party website, a web beacon on the Third Party’s website where baseball products are sold. When Joe, an individual listed in Generation-Z database, visits the baseball website, Generation-Z receives notice by means of the web beacon that Joe visited the baseball site, and Generation-Z would then update Joe’s profile with the information that Joe is interested in baseball. Generation-Z may thereafter present offers of baseball related products and services to Joe. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Generation-Z also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Generation-Z database.  
 _(c)_ New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is Generation-Z’s use of new and evolving technology. As a result, Generation-Z strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

1.5 Outside Information. Generation-Z may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of Generation-Z including information located in public databases (Outside Information).

1.6 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information Generation-Z gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data.

1.7 No Information Collected from Children. Generation-Z will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Generation-Z obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, Generation-Z has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. Generation-Z has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

1.8 Credit Card Information. Generation-Z may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card (Credit Card Information) when an individual completes certain surveys or places an order from Generation-Z. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Generation-Z, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Generation-Z will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase/survey transaction (if applicable), and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. Log File Data: When users log-in to access their account, our servers will automatically record and archive certain information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a Website. These server logs may include information vital to validating the user’s authorization to access the account. Information, such as a Web request, Internet Protocol (the IP) address, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize a user’s entry and activity on the Website.

  2.  **Use of Individual Information.**

2.1 Discretion to Use Information. THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY’S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Generation-Z currently uses Individual Information, but Generation-Z may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted, Generation-Z may update this policy from time to time. Generation-Z may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

2.2 Email. Generation-Z uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Generation-Z may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list.

 _2.2(a)_ Content of Email Messages. In certain commercial email messages sent by Generation-Z, an advertiser’s name will appear in the From: line but hitting the Reply button will cause a reply email to be sent to Generation-Z. The Subject: line of Generation-Z email messages may contain a line provided from the advertiser to Generation-Z.

 _2.2(b)_ Solicited Email. Generation-Z only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Website to receive email from Generation-Z or to individuals who have agreed on Third Party websites to receive email from Third Parties such as Generation-Z. Generation-Z does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Generation-Z email messages.

2.3 Targeted Advertising. Generation-Z uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Generation-Z uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.5 below) to associate an individual with that person’s Individual Information, and Generation-Z attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Generation-Z may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing. Generation-Z uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones.

2.5 Mobile Phone SMS Messaging. In certain cases, when requested by an individual, a Third Party may use Individual Information to provide customized content and advertising via SMS messaging to an individual’s cell phone. Generation-Z is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Third Parties.

2.6 Use of Technology Information. Generation-Z uses Technology Information in the following ways which are including but not limited to: (1) matching a person’s Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person’s online browsing habits on the Internet, and (3) to determine which areas of Generation-Z websites are most frequently visited. This information helps Generation-Z to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Generation-Z can target advertising and promotions to these individuals.

2.7 Profiles of Individuals. Generation-Z uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

2.8 Storage of Individual Information. Generation-Z stores the Individual Information in a database on Generation-Z computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Generation-Z control. Notwithstanding such measures, Generation-Z cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Generation-Z computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

  3.  **Dissemination of Individual Information.**

3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties. Generation-Z MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN GENERATION-Z’S SOLE DISCRETION.

3.2 Order Fulfillment. Generation-Z will transfer Individual Information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such Third Party while using Generation-Z websites or when responding to offers provided by Generation-Z.

3.3 Legal Process. Generation-Z may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.

3.4 Summary Data. Generation-Z may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

3.5 Access. Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting [privacy@generation-z.com](mailto:privacy@generation-z.com). Generation-Z may also grant advertising clients and email services providers access to an individual’s email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected.

  4.  **Privacy Practices of Third Parties.**

4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, Advertisers) who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Generation-Z does not control Advertisers’ use of such technology and Generation-Z has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

4.2 Links. The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties. Generation-Z is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Generation-Z does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

4.3 Affiliated Companies. Generation-Z may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with Generation-Z in Generation-Z’s discretion. Should Generation-Z be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, Generation-Z reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from their Website(s).

  5.  **Individuals Outside of the United States.**

5.1 Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by Generation-Z in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States.

  6.  **Unsubscribe Procedures.**

6.1 If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from Generation-Z, you have several options:

 _(a)_ Unsubscribe from one email list. To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) send an email to [unsubscribe@generation-z.com](mailto:unsubscribe@generation-z.com) or (2) follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by Generation-Z.

 _(b)_ Unsubscribe from all of Generation-Z email lists. We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by Generation-Z. To globally unsubscribe from all of Generation-Z lists, send an email to [unsubscribe@generation-z.com](mailto:unsubscribe@generation-z.com).

 _(c)_ Unsubscribe from a particular SMS messaging campaign. To unsubscribe from a particular SMS messaging campaign on a cell phone, send STOP, END, or QUIT to the SMS message received by the individual. In addition, other methods to unsubscribe may be set forth on the website at which the individual signed up for the SMS messaging campaign.
